In the name of Jesus Christ!
Every knee shall bow!
Every tongue shall confess!
You demon, you familiar spirit,
I command you, in the name of Jesus - out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
We are legion.
CRUSADE IN PERU WITH T.B. JOSHUA
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Victor Moises
18 years old
Testimony From The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I came here looking for my deliverance.
Since I was very small, I felt an attraction towards men
and after some time, when I joined a swimming class, I started dating a man.
I began to touch him and he began to touch me. We began caressing and hugging each other.
Testimony From The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
It didn't allow me to study or concentrate and I would feel disturbed.
I was in the stands at the crusade when I started to cough and then the evil spirit in me manifested.
Then, I was carried to where the prophet was.
During the mass prayer, the evil spirit in me began to manifest.
Testimony From The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I feel much better. I thank God for my deliverance.
Now, I have peace. I thank God.
Now, after my deliverance, I no longer have affection for fellow men
because God has delivered me.
Now, I am at peace and with God's help, I will do better in my studies and will have a career.
My advice is to guard your heart, obey all of God's commandments
and don't open the door to the enemy.
Thank You, Jesus! Thank You for delivering me!